(Raj:)I'm so glad we
could work this all out.
(Penny:)Yeah, me, too.
You know, we
should have dinner
(Emily:)one night with you and Leonard.
(Penny:)Oh, we would love that.
Great!
(both chuckle)
(Penny:)Okay, good night, guys.
All right, night.
(chuckles): Bye.
(Emily and Penny(simultaneously):)I hate her.
I hate her.
(Raj:)I'm really disappointed
we're not gonna have
(Raj:)our own comic book store.
I know.
(Leonard:)I was looking forward to it.
It would've been
(Sheldon:)so nice to have a place
that was ours,
(Sheldon:)where we could just sit
and read comics in peace.
(Howard:)With comfy seats.
(Raj:)And snacks.
(Sheldon:)Well, I guess
it was too good to be true.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(all sigh)